Andriy Kondzolko

Ruby on Rails Developer

267.945.1902 kondzolko@gmail.com

- ✓ **Self-starter** full of ideas and eager to learn, adapt quickly to the changing business environment. Learn by doing, not afraid to ask questions.
- ✓ **Problem Solver** resourceful, think outside the box. I see problems as challenges and try to learn from it. I know when to do a complex thinking and when to go through short cuts to find the best solution.
- ✓ **Leadership** build trusting relationship with both co-workers and clients, earn their respect and lead teams to success.
- ✓ Reliable dedicated worker. Take extra steps to achieve goals, take responsibility for my actions.

Summary of Qualifications

5 years of experience in **Front-End Development** and **3 years** of experience in **Ruby on Rails**. BS in programming. Fluent in core web technologies, contemporary JavaScript libraries and MVC Frameworks. Know how to build and support scalable web applications and complex websites. Can lead the team and manage the projects, good at planning and setting up a workflow. Strong analytical and critical thinking skills.

Technical Competencies

Proficiency with the following: Windows, HTML, XML, CSS, JS, MySQL, jQuery, JSON, SASS, Linux, Unix, Git, Bootstrap, phpMyAdmin, e-Commerce service platforms, LAMP stack development experience. Mid-level Ruby on Rails Developer.

Professional Experience

<u>11/2016 – present</u>

NEARIX, LLC

Ruby on Rails Developer

Software Development Company

Full stack Developer for a major client in the Automotive Industry, responsible for a variety of backend and frontend tasks:

- Contribute to all stages of application development, from UI design to final testing
- Develop backend for APIs (iOS)
- Developing JSON API with message authentication (HMAC-SHA1)
- Integrate client's website with a 3rd party CRM application
- Implement PDF Templates generation via Ruby on Rails
- DB requests and Web App optimization
- Review and inspect code, indicate and fix bugs
- Work on an ongoing basis with UI designers and Product Managers in a team environment

Technologies used in project: Ruby on rails, Ajax, GitHub, CSS, HTML, JavaScript, Unix, OOP, MacOS, Linux, PostGress SQL, XML, Bootstrap 4

08/2015 – 11/2016 AAIT School

Web Administrator

IT School, Feasterville-Trevose, PA

- Create Web services on Watir-webdriver to collect needed information and to promote company's website in Social Media.
- Web Support, bug fixing, database support.

03/2015 - 12/2015

Core Automotive Group

Administrative Manager

Auto Dealer, Philadelphia, PA

- Supporting operations by supervising staff; planning, organizing, and implementing administrative systems.
- Improving program and service quality by devising new applications; updating procedures; evaluating system results with users
- Supervising and motivating 25 employees
- Accomplish staff results by communicating job expectations; planning, monitoring, and appraising job results; coaching, counseling, and disciplining employees; initiating, coordinating, and enforcing systems, policies, and procedures.

01/2014 - 03/2015

Core Automotive Group

IT Media

Web Developer / System Administrator

Auto Dealer, Philadelphia, PA

- Developing Web Applications (RoR, HTML5, CSS3, JS, jQuery, MySQL, Redis)
- Creating and configuring a deployment project (Capistrano)
- Developing the company's website core-automotive.com (Ruby on Rails, HTML5, CSS3, JS, jQuery, Git Hub, Unix, OOP)
- Organizing, Modifying, Supporting and Troubleshooting computer systems.

<u>09/2012 - 09/2013</u>

Web Developer, Head of technical Department, Web Store Administrator.

Marketing & Advertising, Kiev, Ukraine

- Developing Web Applications (Ruby on Rails, HTML5, CSS3)
- SEO, Web Analytics (AdWords, AdSense, Yandex-Direct, Google Analytics)
- Developing Marketing Campaigns (Teaser advertising, Google AdWords)
- Managing Team of 4 people

<u>11/2011 – 08/2012</u> <u>Webicom</u>

Webmaster

Internet Marketing, Lviv, Ukraine

- Developed Web Applications (HTML5, CSS3, MySQL)
- SEO, Web Analytics (Yandex-Direct, Google Analytics)
- Developed network of an online-stores
- Developed automatic content update system (Uploads new items automatically)
- Set up the company's workflow through the SRM System (Megaplan)
- Lead a team of Content Managers
- Set up an automatic Call Center (oktell, IP ATC)

Education

9/2006 - 7/2010

Lviv Polytechnic National University

Lviv, Ukraine

BS in Computer Programming